{
    "id": "fab79b09e4624fb397d72392f30671b4",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Do you enjoy ………………. models from clay?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to make",
                "make",
                "to making",
                "making"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "2ee27b60f5974406a494c4a375488c69"
        },
        {
            "question": "While holidaying in Sydney, Martin  …………….. a strong Australian accent.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "caught",
                "acquired",
                "earned",
                "gained"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ceb181a2c0394ce995cbbad7e5ab19e6"
        },
        {
            "question": "...................... he was, he played well.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though tired",
                "Tired though",
                "As tired",
                "Although tired"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "12f6fc76ec2c49e6ae05cc9b2b883de7"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. she was, she could not react at all.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though shocked",
                "Although shocked",
                "Shocked as",
                "As shocked"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5897dae438ab4312baa563f0b0f9d0e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The front door was open, ……………… nobody was at home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "but",
                "and",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "55d9b81c3c32456090a8378db36010bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "The bell has already .......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rang",
                "ring",
                "rung",
                "ringing"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5859fcd2993c4f969ec8ced8e29eaea8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Stella ………………….. wait for her birthday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can hardly",
                "can't hardly",
                "won't hardly",
                "couldn't hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1b501716215e47d8bfdeb800dce31c8c"
        },
        {
            "question": "There were ………………… students in the class than expected.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "fewer",
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b9032c69d45a4d5685c1bc00f1c798c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I did ..................... work today than yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "lesser",
                "few",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0ad2225d0e464559a0d25b91b83f3939"
        },
        {
            "question": "Dad has …………………. on the sofa all morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lay",
                "laid",
                "lain"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8c6d5205a97b4760a6db7b400f37bb4d"
        }
    ]
}